Mss.B.B585
American Philosophical Society
- Selected Inventory from Genetics Subject Guide
  - Muller, Hermann Joseph, 1920-1954; Correspondence ( 22 items )
    Cytogenetics; Genetics; Genetics of plants; Smith College
  - Northrop, John Howard, 1926; Correspondence ( 3 items )
  - Randolph, Lowell Fitz, 1924-1948; Correspondence ( 25 items )
    Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Cytogenetics; Genetics of plants; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Zea (maize) genetics
  - Robbins, William J., 1928-1954; Correspondence ( 34 items )
    Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Educational matters; Evolution; Genetics of plants; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Russian politics and science -- Vavilov, Nikolai Ivanovich
  - Satina, Sophie, 1922-1954; Correspondence ( 36 items )
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Fellowships, assistantships; Publication; Research support; Smith College
  - Schramm, Jacob Richard, 1921-1952; Correspondence ( 30 items )
    Editorial matters; Publication -- Biological Abstracts; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - Shull, George Harrison, 1909-1948; Correspondence ( 90 letters )
    Bibliographical matters; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Biographical and personal data -- Vries, Hugo de; Botany and plant genetics; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Cytogenetics; Editorial matters -- Genetics; Genetics of plants; Publication; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Teaching -- Harvard University; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Sinnott, Edmund W., 1916-1953; Correspondence ( 325 items )
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Biographical and personal data; Botany and plant genetics; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Connecticut Argicultural College; Genetics of plants; Human genetics; International Congress of Genetics -- Sixth Congress; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Political issues; Publication; Recommendations; Russian politics and science -- Vavilov, Nikolai Ivanovich; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Teaching; World War I -- Impact on science
  - Smith College, Genetics Experiment Station, 1946-1955; Records ( 7 folders )
    Conferences and symposia; Educational matters; Genetics of plants; Graduate study; Smith College
  - Stanley, Wendell M. (Wendell Meredith), 1942-1943; Correspondence ( 5 items )
  - Thaxter, Roland, 1904-1928; Correspondence ( 27 items )
    Botany and plant genetics; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Thaxter, Roland. 70th birthday; Teaching -- University of Halle--Blakeslee, Albert Francis
  - Tukey, Harold Bradford, 1944-1951; Correspondence ( 31 items )
    Conferences and symposia; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Smith College
  - van Overbeek, Johannes, 1942-1950; Correspondence ( 35 items )
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Biographical and personal data; Botany and plant genetics; Conferences and symposia; Embryology, developmental genetics; Genetics of plants; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Publication
  - Van Slyke, Donald D. (Donald Dexter), 1952; Correspondence ( 1 item )
  - Weston, William H., Jr., 1922-1943; Correspondence ( 45 items )
    Biographical and personal data; Botany and plant genetics; Thaxter, Roland; Travel -- South America
  - Wetmore, Ralph H., 1944-1954; Correspondence ( 34 items )
    Conferences and symposia; Harvard University; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - Wright, Benjamin F., 1949-1954; Correspondence ( 23 items )
    Biographical and personal data; Research support; Smith College
  - Ziegler, Irmgard, 1958-1976; Correspondence ( 60 items )
    Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Drosophila genetics; Editorial matters; Fellowships, assistantships; Immunogenetics; Molecular genetics; Political issues -- Germany